nice to meet you.
初めまして
It's so cute.
めっちゃ可愛いですね
is that so?
そうですか?
Black hair suits you.
黒髪似合いますね
That pad is rare.
なかなかないよ、そのパッドの
Is it true?
本当ですか?
Well, the camera is already rolling.
で、もうカメラ回っちゃってるんですけど
Is that what it feels like?
そんな感じ?
I thought you didn't have it?
持ってなくと思ったの?
I thought I didn't have it.
持ってないと思った
It's spinning, actually.
回ってますよ、実は
I'm nervous.
緊 張してます
Because I can't make eye contact with you.
なかなか目を合わせてくれないから
I wonder if he's nervous.
緊 張してるのかな、みたいな
Well then, to relieve the tension, let's have a little chat.
じゃあ、緊張をほぐすというか、 ちょっと軽くおしゃべりを言
I would like to know if there is one,
って いるか、 知りたいなと思って、
May I?
いいですか?
Even if I ask a lot of things.
色々聞いちゃっても
it's okay.
大丈夫です
It's fine as long as you can answer.
答えられる範囲でいいんで
What do you usually do?
普段は何をされている方なんですか?
I'm a student.
学 生です
学生だ
Young one.
若いもん
Can I tell you where I'm going back?
どこに帰ったりとか言えたりする?
I'm in my second year at a psychiatric university.
精神大学2年です
2 years?
2年?
I see.
そうか
Oh, sorry.
あ、ごめんね
Isn't that good?
いいじゃないですかって
Like, you like me.
俺が好きだな、みたいな
Sorry.
ごめんね
What is that?
それは何?
teaching?
教学?
Women's college?
女子大?
It's a women's university.
女子大です
女子大なんだ
Same goes for women's colleges.
女子大にそう
Are you a spiritual woman?
精神女子か
It sounds good.
響きいいね
Like a young lady.
お嬢様みたいな
I guess so.
そうかな
The hairstyle and hair color also match,
髪型とか、 髪色とかも合い合って、
It looks like a really boxy collar.
凄 い箱襟みたいな
I have an image in mind.
イメージ持っちゃうんですけど
Is it quite like that?
結構そんな感じ?
Is your family quite wealthy?
実家が結構お金持ち系?
I wonder what it is?
どうなんだろう?
Not really.
そうでもない
Is it normal?
普通なのか?
It's pretty solid.
結構しっかりしてるところ
Are you strong, young lady?
お嬢様、しっかりしてる?
I think it's solid.
しっかりしてると思います
By the way, what are you studying in your undergraduate degree?
ちなみに今、学部は 何を勉強してるの?
What was your undergraduate degree?
学 部 は何だったか?
General Department.
総合本科部
That's annoying.
ムズイっすね
The subordinate administration is also working hard.
部下政権も頑張ってます
Are you working hard?
頑張ってる?
School is fun.
学校楽しい
学校は楽しいです
Do you play law or something?
法学とか遊んだりする?
What do you play?
何して遊ぶの?
I like going to take pictures with my friends.
友達と、 フリクラ撮りに行ったりとか
nice.
いい ね
Maybe I'll go to the game center.
ゲームセンター行ったりするかな
That's right.
そうなんだ
That's what I like.
そういうの好きなの
What game is it at the game center?
ゲームセンターとさ、 何のゲーム?
Do you play games?
ゲームする?
Free club?
フリクラ?
Like crane games.
クレーンゲームとか
It's a crane game.
クレーンゲームなんだ
Like taking pictures of dolls.
人形撮ったりとか
Do you take pictures of dolls?
人形撮ったりする?
A stuffed animal?
ぬいぐるみとか?
Do you put those pictures on your bed?
それ撮ったやつをさ、 ベッドに並べてたりするの?
I'm lining it up.
並べてる
nice.
いいね
Can you imagine it?
イメージできる?
I can imagine it.
イメージできる
I may be biased, but I saw stuffed animals lined up,
偏見かもしれないけど、 ぬいぐるみとか並べてて、
Are you sleeping together?
一緒に眠ってるでしょ?
We're sleeping together.
一緒に眠ってます
Is the piano color also pink?
ピアノ色もピンク貴重?
After all, it's all pink and white.
やっぱりピンクと白で統一してるか
That's good.
いいっすね
After all, pajamas are fluffy pajamas?
パジャマとかやっぱり、 モコモコ系のパジャマ?
It might be fluffy.
モコモコしてるかもしれない
After all, it's still fluffy.
だって今もモコモコしてるもんね
It's definitely fluffy.
モコモコしてる確かに
I'm feeling fluffy.
モ コモコしてる
It feels good.
気持ちいいっすね
Fashion check.
ファッションチェック
Fashion check?
ファッションチェック?
It's fluffy.
モコモコしてる
You're so fluffy, aren't you?
モ コ モ コ してるよね
sorry.
ごめんなさい
what up?
どうした?
I thought it was embarrassing.
恥ずかしいなと思って
Are you embarrassed?
恥ずかしいの?
I see.
そうか
It's interesting, seriously.
面白いですね、マジで
Do you like skirts?
スカート好きなの?
I only have the skirt.
スカートしか持ってない
Is that so?
そうなの?
It feels like a girl.
女の子って感じですね
I just saw it, are your legs thin?
今見えたんだけどさ、 足細い?
Your legs are thin.
足細いよね
Is it your feet?
足ですか?
Is that so?
そういうのかな?
Anmari.
あ ん まり
It's really thin.
めっちゃ細いよね
Don't compare yourself to those around you?
周りと比べない?
That kid is fat.
あの子デブだなって
There's no comparison like that.
そんな比べないんですよ
Even now, it was a long process.
今もさ、手長かったもん
A little hand.
ちょっと手
Hey, can I have a look?
ほら、見せてもらっていい?
It's so beautiful.
めっちゃ綺麗じゃん
Fat is better.
デブの方がいいね
It's long.
長いです
The style is really nice.
スタイルめっちゃいいじゃん
Are you doing any circles now?
今なんかサークルとかやってたりするの?
I don't do it anymore.
もうやってないです
Haven't you done it?
やってないんだ?
Did you do anything originally?
もともとなんかやってた?
copper?
どう?
Kyudou.
キュウドウ
Not Archin, but Kyudou.
アーチリンじゃなく、キュウドウ
Did you play Kyudou?
キュウドウやったんですか?
nice.
いいね
It looks like something you could imagine in a picture.
絵に描いたらいい感じの あれっすね
Kyudou, can I have you look at my hand again?
キュウドウ、もう一回手見してもらっていい?
The hand that was doing Kyudou.
キュウドウやってた手
It's beautiful and soft.
綺麗で柔らかいね
Are you suddenly connecting?
いきなり繋ぐの?
I thought there might be some.
ちょっとあるかなと思って
I feel like I was playing Kyudou.
キュウドウやってた感じが
Is that so?
そういうこと?
Can I have a look?
見せてもらっていい?
Huh?
えっ?
It's kind of cute.
可愛いな、なんか
So cute.
めっちゃ可愛い
I don't interact with men too much,
あんまり男の人と 触れ合うのとか、
Don't you have much experience?
あんまり経験ないですか?
do not have.
ない
What about girls?
女子でなんなの?
There's no chance to interact with each other.
触れ合う機会はないよね
No.
ないです
Do you have a boyfriend?
彼氏さんとかいるの?
There isn't one.
いないね
He's not there.
いないんだ
Do you want it?
欲しいと思う?
I wonder if I'll want it someday.
いつかは欲しいかなって
It's fun now.
今は楽しい
With a girl.
女の子と一緒に
Girls' age.
女子代
Isn't there a blind date or something?
なんか合コンとかない?
Girls' age.
女子代
Group date?
合コン?
I wonder if I've ever been there.
行ったことないかな
Is he a little different from the men who come to such places?
そういうところに来る男とは ちょっと違う?
Do you think it's kind of funny?
なんかチャラいなって思う?
Hey, you might think that.
ちょっと、それは思うかもしれない
If you're talking to a guy, all of a sudden.
もし男の人と喋ってて いきなり いきなりね
Do you think this is how you felt?
こんな感じにされたと思う?
Huh?
えっ?
What, what is it?
なん なんなんなんだっか?
No, the guys who come to blind parties are a bit flirtatious.
いやいや、 合コンとかに来る男の人は ちょっとチャラいなって
You said you had an impression on me,
印 象を持ってるって言ってたから、
Well, you don't do that kind of thing, do you?
え、 そういうことはしなくないですか?
I'm wondering if I should do something like this.
なんか こういうことするとこどうかなって思ってる
No, no, no, no.
いや いや いや、だめですよ
picture?
え?
No?
だめ?
I don't think they will do that.
そういうことはしないと思います
Ah, but now, let's try something a little different.
あ、でも今さ、 ちょっと違ってみたでしょ
I just went to the bottom of the message.
今ちょっとメッセージ下に行ってたよ
Oh, I was still watching it.
あら、今も見てたね
be on one's mind?
気になる?
What caught your attention?
気になったやつ?
a little bit?
ちょっと?
Well, I'm curious.
まあ、気になるよね
Because she's cute, she's already grown up.
可愛いからさ、 もう大きくなっちゃった
Look, look, look.
見て見て見て
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
But today, I brought my camera too.
でも、 今日さ、 カメラも持ってさ、
That's right.
そうですよね
What do you do?
どういうことするんですか?
In front of the camera today.
今日 カメラの前で
When?
いつのこと?
picture?
え?
what?
何?
It's nothing.
なんでもないです
I couldn't hear it just now.
今ちょっと聞こえなかった
sorry.
ごめん
It just exploded, right?
今 爆発もしたでしょ?
explosion?
爆発?
Because it was covered.
被っちゃったから
What will you do today?
今日はどういうことをしますか?
Are you saying?
言うんですか?
I'll do it.
しちゃうよね
Don't you know?
わかんない?
I don't have much experience.
あんまり経験ない
I wonder if I have any experience.
経験ないかな
So, have you ever done it alone?
で、一人でしたことはある?
Have you ever done it alone?
一人でしたことはあるかな
Is there one?
あるの?
There is.
ありますよ
That's true.
それはありますよ
Do it alone.
一人ですること
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
I'm too embarrassed to say it.
恥ずかしくて言えない
If you don't tell me, you won't be able to proceed.
言わないと、 すすむないですか?
Are you alone?
一人でする?
what?
何?
After I said so.
俺が言ってって言ってからね
Say ta chin.
タ チンって言って
sorry.
ごめん
What does it mean to be alone?
一人ですることは何ということ?
I wonder if I will.
しちゃうかな
What do you have as a side dish?
何をおかずにしてる?
What should I say?
なんて言えばいいの?
Do you see anything?
何か見るのか?
When you're delusional.
妄想のとき
It's a delusion.
妄想ですね
Maybe that's how I feel now.
多分今の感覚
Push or something.
推しとか
favorite?
推 し?
Imagine it and touch it yourself.
想像して、 自分で触っちゃおう
Where should I touch it?
どこ触っちゃおう?
By hand.
手で
By hand?
手で?
here.
ここ
Right here?
ここでしょ?
here.
ここ
Do you touch it alone?
一 人で触るの?
You can't say it properly, soot.
ちゃんと言えないんじゃ、 すす
No.
ま ない
different?
違う?
The important thing about me is
自分のその大事なところは、
It's cute.
可愛 いね
It's delicious.
よいおいしいね
I have various hobbies,
俺はさ、 いろいろ趣味で、
Are you mentally prepared?
心 の準備OK?
I will do my best.
頑張ります
It's like Ande.
アンデみたいになってます
I will do my best.
頑張ります
I can't say enough.
よく言いかないです
There's one thing I want you to say
一個言ってほしいことがあ
So, today, I'll do my best to take some naughty pictures.
って、 今日は、えっちの撮影頑張ります
May I?
いいですか?
it's okay.
大丈夫です
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
TRUE?
本当?
It's cute.
可愛いじゃん
The hair is so-so.
髪、そらそらだね
Very sora sora.
めっちゃそらそら
It was too late, and I was getting carried away.
そらそらすぎて、 すーせられていっちゃって
Is that so?
そういうこと?
What shampoo do you use?
何のシャンプー使ってるの?
Panten?
パンテン?
different.
違う
Ichikamu?
イチカム?
Are you using it?
使ってる?
That's right.
そうだよね
Your face is red.
顔赤いな
hot.
熱い
Hot, hot.
熱 い熱い
I get nervous.
緊張しちゃうもん
hey.
ね
I can't get angry.
怒 られない
I don't get angry.
怒られない
Isn't it wrong?
違うでしょ?
It's too cute, I can't resist it.
可愛すぎるから、 我慢できない
wait a minute.
ちょっと待って
hang on.
待って
picture?
え?
Why?
何で?
picture?
え?
Huh?
あれ?
Don't like it?
嫌?
Are you taking pictures of me too?
俺のことも写してる?
Did you hate it?
嫌だった?
I don't hate it, but I thought it would come all of a sudden.
嫌 じゃないけど、 いきなり来るんだと思って
It was a little too strong.
ちょっと勢い強すぎた
Suddenly?
いきなり?
difficult.
難しい
It's difficult, isn't it?
難 しい ですよね
Well then, it's true that things can come suddenly,
じゃあ、 確かに、いきなり来るもあるので、
First, let's start with the hug.
まず、はぐから始めようか
First, let's start with what sticks together.
まず、くっつくところから始めていこうか
Sounds good, right?
なんかいいよね?
Well then,
じゃあ、
Let's show you what's important about us.
自 分の大事なところを見せていこう
Guidance?
お手引き?
Huh?
あれ?
Do you have a clue?
お手引き当たってる?
I did it.
しちゃったね
I don't dislike it.
嫌じゃない
Are you going to say it?
もって、言うの?
I saw it.
見えた
be on one's mind?
気になる?
be on one's mind.
気になる
I've been watching it for a while now.
見ちゃってるよ、さっきから
I've been watching quite a lot.
結構見ちゃってる
By the way, did you know that schools do this kind of thing?
ちなみにさ、 学校の こういうことをしてるって知ってんの?
You don't know.
知らないよね
In front of the camera, you have to know.
カメラの前でさ、知らないと
i don't know?
知らない?
No.
だめだよ
It's too much trouble.
めんどくしゃくしちゃって
a little bit.
ちょっと
experiment
実験
I might get a part-time job,
とか バイトしちゃうかもしれないけど、
Wait a minute.
ちょっとしちゃって
No.
ダメ
It's not bad.
ダメじゃないよ
Because that's what we're doing today.
だって今日こういうことするんだよ
Isn't that no good?
ダ メじゃないか
Also, are you going to watch a lot of Fukappu?
あとね、フカップいっぱい見ちゃう?
Chan
ちゃん
and.
と
It's smooth.
す べすべだね
You're young.
若いね
What year are you in university?
大学何年生だ?
2nd year student.
2年生
2nd year university student.
大学2年生
It's still smooth.
まだすべすべだね
Smooth.
すべすべ
what up?
どうした?
What kind of place is this?
ここなんてとこだっけ?
Make it easy to see.
見やすいように
Look, look.
ほら、見して
Here, put your hand here.
ほら、手をここ
white and pink.
白とピンク
Well then, I want to see more of your pants.
じゃあさ、 パンツももっと見たいからさ、
Please just lift this leg.
足こっちだけ上げてもらって
Will your face stop?
顔もやむの?
Yeah, yeah.
そうそうそう
Are you going to put your hands up?
手をアップルするの?
Yeah, yeah.
そうそうそう
No, if the door is too close up, you won't be able to see it.
いや、ドアアップすぎたらね、 映んないんだよ
Because it gets blurry.
ぼやけちゃうから
Should I take a look at it carefully?
大事に見てみる?
Isn't it visible?
映ってない?
It doesn't show up, right?
映ってないでしょ?
It's reflected.
映ってる
Tell me yourself.
自分で教えて
finger.
指を
The place I always touch myself.
いつも自分で触っているところ
Does it feel good?
気持ちいい?
Feels good.
気持ちいい
myself?
自分?
Just like that.
そのまま
I am a second year student at Shinsei Women's University.
精神女子大学2年生です
Let's talk together today.
今日も一緒にお話します
Go to Spiritual Women's University
精神女子大学に行
That's what I'm saying.
って くる
Do you want to go with me?
一緒に行きたい?
Well then,
じゃあ、
Come.
来 いで
I really like the style.
めっちゃスタイルいいね
Her skin is also white.
肌も白い
Can I come closer?
近づいていい?
Yeah.
うん
I really like looking at the side of my bra.
俺、ブラのさ、 横のところ見るのすごく好きなんだよ
On the side?
横 の ところ?
Yeah, I have a fetish for that.
うん、そこフェチで
Can I ask you to raise your hand just once?
一回手を挙げてもらっていい?
Yeah, I have a fetish for that.
うん、そこフェチで
close.
近い
It's close.
近いね
It's completely different from what you see on top of your clothes, as I said before.
服の上からと全然違うんだよ、さっきと
Na
な
To?
に?
what?
な に?
eat?
食べ る?
Stretch your legs.
足伸ばしちゃって
It's huge
めっちゃでか
Yes.
い ね
Beautiful shape.
形きれい
This is so beautiful.
これ、めっちゃきれいじゃん
Hey?
ねえ?
yes.
そう
Since when is it big?
いつぐらいから大き
Has it become dark?
く なったの?
Junior high school students...
中学生...
Is it from time?
時からかな?
Since time?
時から?
Yeah.
うん
Junior high school students...
中学生の...
12 and.
12と
No, it wasn't that big back then.
いや、その時はこんなに大きくないけど
Are your classmates not looking at you?
同級生とかに見られてない?
What, you haven't seen it?
え、見られてない?
Oh, sorry.
あ、ごめん
Try being in front of the camera.
カメラの前でいってみて
At the back.
後ろで
Is your part-time job over now?
今バイト終わり?
Are you okay?
大丈夫なの?
So at a time like this.
じゃあこんな時間に
picture?
え?
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
What are you doing?
なにしてる?
da
ダ
Me jan.
メ じゃん
Solid bottom.
しっかりな下
Hey?
ね え?
It's muscular.
筋できてる
See, this makes sense.
ほ ら、これ筋できてる
This is what I want you to tell me.
これさ、 教えてほしいんだけどさ
Shall I tell you?
教えてあげよっか
It's a muscle.
筋ってよ
what?
なに?
gum
ガム
...
Gum?
ガ ム?
Isn't it a nuisance?
邪魔じゃない?
When did it happen?
いつの間になってる?
Get your hands on it.
手ついて
Hands up.
手を上にして
Make it towards the top.
上の方にして
I mean, let's move it from that hand.
あの手からずらすっていうか
Muscle mission.
筋のミッション
Raise your feet.
足上げて
both and
両方と
too.
も
No.
ダ メだ
I can't stand it anymore.
もう、 我慢できないっすね
I don't really check it
別にチェックしないんだ
Yo.
よ
Sorry
ご め
Nah, that's it.
んな さい
It's very rounded.
めっちゃ丸めえだよ
Have you ever expanded it yourself?
自分で広げたことある?
do not have.
ない
It's like this.
こんな感じ
terrible.
やばい
Because he's a man.
男だからさ
I don't really understand it.
よく分かってなくてさ
I'd like you to tell me.
教えてほしいんだけどさ
I'm expanding it now.
今広げてるから
Can I touch you now?
さっき触っていい?
It might be cool.
かっこいいかも
There's a hole here.
穴あるじゃん、ここに
A hole that says a lot.
ピチャピチャ言っちゃう穴
There is a small hole above it.
その上に小さい穴ある
What to do?
何するところ?
Where to sleep?
寝るところ?
It hurts if it gets into my hair.
毛に落ちんちめたら痛いから
Shall I ring it with my fingers?
指で鳴らそうか
Okay, hands.
いいよ、手
Can I take it easy?
楽にしていい?
So, put your elbows on it.
そこで、 肘つけ
Then tell me to lick your pussy.
じゃあ、 おまんこ舐めてって言って
be on one's mind?
気になる?
Being licked.
舐められて
be on one's mind.
気になる
be on one's mind?
気になる?
Can you get it here?
ここに手つける?
Put your hands up.
手を立てて
Try standing it up.
立 ててみて
touch?
触る?
There's a chance.
チャンスがある
It hurts, it hurts.
痛い、痛い
Totally painful.
完全に痛い
it hurts?
痛い?
Remember Feller?
フ ェラーのこと覚えてる?
Yeah.
うん
good?
いい?
Can I come in?
入 れていい?
Pussy.
おまんこ
Why do you include it?
なんで入れるの?
Well, that's right.
まあまあ、そうっすね
I want to imitate you in person
生 し寄ったまねしたいんだけど
difference.
さ
What I lived
生 したこと
be?
ある?
be.
ある
In the pussy of a second year student at Shinsei Women's University
精 神女子大学2年生の おまんこに
While making peace.
ピ ースしながら
piece?
ピース?
Psychiatric female college 2nd year student
精 神 女 子 大 学2年生
2nd year student at Shinsei Women's University
の 精 神女子大学2年生
Please lick the pussy of a second year student at Shinsei Women's University.
の 精 神女子大学2年生の おまんこ舐めてください
I can enter.
入 れるよ
Where is the milk?
ど こ に 乳 が入ってる?
ど こに乳が入ってる?
Well then,
じゃあ、
I fell down on my upper body.
上 半身で倒れて
So, put your feet up.
じゃあ、 足上げて
Put your feet up behind my hands.
俺の手の後ろに 足上げて
Can you move?
動ける?
It's difficult though.
難しいけど
Keep your hands in front of you
そのまま手を前にして
Try pressing it in a strange place.
変 わった場所で押しよう
Looks like I'm about to go.
そろそろ行きそう
Can I take it out?
出していい?
No.
ダメだ
So I got it all.
だから全部入っちゃったよ
I went in.
入っちゃった
Now, come on, clean your hair and wait.
さあ、 じゃあさあ、 髪をきれいにしてくれて 待って
Get on your elbows again.
もう一度、ひじついて
Do you understand what parent-child surgery feels like?
親子手術感覚分かった?
I think I understand.
分かったと思う
It was my first time growing and it felt good.
初めての生えっちゃ 気持ちよかったですって